The final hunt begins.
Blade: Trinity is a action, horror, science fiction
film directed by David S. Goyer.
For years, Blade has fought against the vampires in the cover of the night.
But now, after falling into the crosshairs of the FBI, he is forced out into the daylight, where he is driven
to join forces with a clan of human vampire hunters he never knew existed—The Nightstalkers.
Together with Abigail and Hannibal, two deftly trained Nightstalkers, Blade follows a trail of
blood to the ancient creature that is also hunting him—the original vampire, Dracula.
Eric Brooks / Blade, played by Wesley Snipes.
Abigail Whistler, played by Jessica Biel.
Hannibal King, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Abraham Whistler, played by Kris Kristofferson.
Dracula / Drake, played by Dominic Purcell.
Danica Talos, played by Parker Posey.
Blade: Trinity is a 2004 American superhero film based
on the Marvel Comics character Blade.
It is the sequel to Blade II (2002) and the third
installment in the Blade franchise.
Written and directed by David S.
Goyer, it stars Wesley Snipes as the title character, alongside Ryan Reynolds, Jessica
Biel, Kris Kristofferson, Dominic Purcell, Parker Posey, and Triple H.
Vampire leader Danica Talos has framed Blade for numerous murders, and
alongside a team of rogue vampire hunters he must fight Dracula.
Blade: Trinity was released in the United States on December 8, 2004.
The film grossed $132 million at the box office worldwide on a budget of $65 million and received mostly negative reviews
from critics for its formulaic themes, directing, and acting; it is the worst-reviewed film in the trilogy.
The film was followed by a television series, Blade: The Series,
in 2006, with Sticky Fingaz replacing Snipes.
Marvel regained the film rights to the character in 2012.
Snipes reprised his role as Blade in the 2024 film Deadpool &
Wolverine, which starred Reynolds as Deadpool.
A reboot film set in the Marvel Cinematic Universe and starring
Mahershala Ali has been in development since 2019.
The film explores themes of martial arts, loss of
loved one, vampire, fbi, superhero.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.